# Jai Shukla

Sasaram, Bihar, India



jaissm002@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/jai-shukla-56041016a

# Summary

I'm a first year undergraduate student. I have keen interest in Cyber Security and Web Development. Being a tech enthusiast, I love to explore and gain more knowledge about the latest technologies. As A Developer, I Enjoy Bridging The Gap Between Functionality And Design. My Goal Is To Always Build Applications That Are Scalable And Efficient Under The Hood While Providing Engaging, Pixel-Perfect User Experiences. In Addition, I Am Highly Responsive To Client Needs And Also Committed To Helping People Realize Their Vision.

# **Experience**



### Web Development & Designing

The Sparks Foundation

May 2021 - Jun 2021 (2 months)

Selected as a Web Development Intern Developed a Webpage asking for donation and Razorpay payment Gateway to get donations

## The Uplift Project

GirlScript Foundation

Jun 2021 - Jul 2021 (2 months)

Selected as a participant in Web Development

#### **Education**



#### Gopal Narayan Singh University

Bachelor Of Computer Application, Computer Science

2020 - 2023

BCA is a three year undergraduate programme in the field of computer science and information technology.



#### Veer Kunwar Singh University, Arrah

Intermidiate, Computer Science 2018 - 2020

Qualifies my 12th from State board



### **Scottish Central School**

Matric, Science 2017 - 2018 I was in 10th standard

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

- Sololearn
- Introduction to cybersecurity Cisco
- Introduction to Programming Using HTML and CSS Udemy Free Courses
- Python Data Structures Coursera Course Certificates

# **Skills**

Robotics • HTML • Python (Programming Language) • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Android Studio • WordPress • Linux • Ethical Hacking • Cybersecurity • JavaScript